christianaudio.com 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy - Audiobooks, MP3, M4B, iPhone Apps, Free Downloads!

Last revised: April 7, 2011

### Privacy Policy & Notice

christianaudio takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

#### What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy covers how christianaudio treats personal information that christianaudio collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that christianaudio does not own or control, or to people that christianaudio does not employ or manage.

#### General Information Collection and Use

  * christianaudio collects personal information when you register with us and when you visit christianaudio pages.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address and zip code. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, telephone number, and Credit Card number.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * christianaudio does not rent or sell personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with christianaudio under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers from us and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of christianaudio’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if christianaudio is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * christianaudio may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria.
    * christianaudio does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

#### Cookies

  * christianaudio may set and access christianaudio cookies on your computer.
  * christianaudio may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to christianaudio’s cookies.

#### Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

  * You can edit your christianaudio.com Information at any time.
  * You can contact christianaudio.com customer service for requests to permanently delete your personal information from our system.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to christianaudio’s service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the christianaudio Newsletter, that are considered part of your christianaudio account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

#### Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have safeguards in place to protect personal information about you.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * christianaudio may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your christianaudio account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

#### Questions and Suggestions

Please feel free to suggest ways we can improve. If you have any concerns about your privacy on our site, please contact us immediately:

eChristian, Inc. & christianaudio.com   
Website Customer Care   
2235 Enterprise Street; Suite 140   
Escondido, CA 92029   
United States of America   
(760) 745-2411
